# **AVRIL, KYUNG-HEE. KIM**

avril.kim@me.com · +82-10-2749-1207 · Seoul, South Korea

#### **Objective**

Seeking a position that will allow me to utilize my strong front end background in javascript, html5, css3 and responsive web coding.

### professional summary

I am interested in trendy web design and dynamic effect. I think my strength point is my passion of new things. that often takes me new subject. and I try to learn by myself like after-effect, canvas even flash as well.

During the work experience In pulip web agency, every single time, I work with different member defence on clients and projects. We always try to make a best quality and our client happy with our result.

#### skills

- HTML5, CSS3, bootstrap
- Javascript

- Photoshop, Illustration
- After-effect, flash

### experience

#### **Front End Developer**

PULIP Communications, Web Agency (2014.11- current)

- backed by jQuery and other Javascript frameworks to enable optimum user experience throughout the site.
- Worked in a deadline driven environment to provide valuable feedback in successful development to ensure client satisfaction.
- Created Flash templates for banner ads to be used as a company standard for online advertisements.
- Worked with variety project team and client follow project.

Major customers : samsung SDS, gore-tex Korea, titleist, larocheposay cosmetic, IBK bank, citi bank

#### Front End Developer / Designer

ING IS, Web Agency (2013.2 - 2014.4)

- HTML, CSS coding of front-end interfaces including cross-browser support and uit testing to ensure quality work.
- Sole front end developer and designer for small company.
- Annual site maintenance for construction company.
- Key responsibilities include creating websites, purchase pages, microsites and other edited products photos.

## project details

2016. 9 - current	IBK online finance renewal project Javascript, jQuery UI, cross-browsing.
2015. 4 - current	larocheposay cosmetic - jQuery, flash, make promotion page
2015. 2 - current	Gore-tex Korea's site maintenance and promotion handling Javascript, flash-action script.
2015. 12 - 2016. 10	Dongbu insurance, Inc Flash contents debug, develop flash- action script.
2015. 7 - 2015.12	Citi bank, Korea renewal website - jQuery, coding for web accessibility
2015. 3 - 2016. 8	MAIIM cosmetic Renewal part of website and mobile site and maintenance jQuery, html, css.
2015. 2 - 2016. 8	Samsung DS - screen-saver for window and mac jQuery for responsive web.
2014. 10 - 2015. 2	Bean Project, roastery and coffee shop - html, css, jQuery + library - cafe24(shopping mall template like wordpress)
2013	ING is, - made variety type of responsive web template html5, css3, jQuery, 1140 grid, 960 grid
2012 - 2014	Luyangel boutique, online - brand web designer - business card, sign, label for clothes, package, image adjust, banner

### education

2013. HBI technical research center Applications of Javascript.

- html5, css3, canvas.
- node.js, angular.js

2008 - 2010

Yuhan college, South Korea

Bachelor's degree, Fashion design.

- GPA - 3.9 / 4.5